Miriam Shukhman

Phone: +972542565362
Email: miriamsh888@gmail.com
GitHub: github.com/MirShukhman
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/miriam-shukhman-2b0a19169

SUMMARY

After seven years as a Paramedic, I am looking to find my footing in the Web Development world. First being exposed to coding through friends I signed up to the Full Stack course in the John Bryce academy without any coding experience or true understanding of what the course entails. Gradually, I fell in love with coding and web development, and was able to develop some neat projects in just under 10 months, from zero knowledge to Full Stack. Being a Paramedic comes with many challenges, especially during pandemic and war times, and while I thoroughly enjoyed my time on the job and learnt a lot of valuable skills, such as working swiftly and efficiently under pressure, learning quickly, and thinking on my feet, I am ready for new and different challenges and exited to venture on my journey in the tech world.

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Python, HTML, CSS, JS, JSX, SQL
- Frameworks: React.js, Flask, Django
- Technologies: MSSQL, Docker, Git, Azure
- Fluent in Languages: Hebrew, English, Russian

EDUCATION

John Bryce Academy - Full Stack Web Development Course

Ariel University - Emergency Medical Technology: Paramedic

MAY 2023 - MAR 2024

SEP 2015 - MAY 2017

EXPERIENCE

John Bryce Academy - Full Stack Web Development Student

MAY 2023 - MAR 2024

- Full Stack Development of Web Applications.
- Working with Microsoft SQL Server database.
- Utilization of Python, Flask, Django and SQLAlchemy for Back-end Development.
- Utilization of React, HTML and CSS for Front-end Development.
- Deployment of web applications using Docker and Azure.

TEREM - Paramedic

MAY 2017 - PRESENT

- Emergency medical services and procedures.
- Triaging patients and Managing patient flow throughout the clinic.

TEREM - Nursing Staff Manager

AUG 2019 - AUG 2020

- Managing Nursing Staff and Inventory in a clinic branch.
- Adapting and overcoming daily challenges during COVID-19 pandemic.

IDF Budgeting Unit - Budgeting Assistant

OCT 2017 - OCT 2019

- Managing budgets of military units under Central District Command's supervision.
- Second Year Head of Budgeting 340th Division

Sha'arei Zedek Hospital - Medical Secretary in L&D Unit Sprinzak Cafeteria - Barista and Cashier SEP 2015 - MAY 2017